goingluxury.com 2019-03-23

# Privacy Policy | Going Luxury

Company Privacy policy

1\. Introduction

1.1 We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors and service users; in this policy we explain how we will handle your personal data.

1.2 By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

1.3 Our website incorporates privacy controls which affect how we will process your personal data. By using the privacy controls, you can specify whether you would like to receive direct marketing communications and limit the publication of your information. You can access the privacy controls by contacting us at legal@2bookaholiday.com

2\. How we use your personal data

2.1 In this Section 3 we have set out:

(a) the general categories of personal data that we may process;

(b) in the case of personal data that we did not obtain directly from you, the source and specific categories of that data;

(c) the purposes for which we may process personal data; and

(d) the legal bases of the processing.

2.2 We may process data about your use of our website and services (“usage data”). The usage data may include your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. The source of the usage data is our analytics tracking system. This usage data may be processed for the purposes of analysing the use of the website and services. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely monitoring and improving our website and services.

2.3 We may process your account data (“account data”). The account data may include your name and email address. The source of the account data is you. The account data may be processed for the purposes of operating our website, providing our services, ensuring the security of our website and services, maintaining back-ups of our databases and communicating with you. The legal basis for this processing is consent.

2.4 We may process your information included in your personal profile on our website (“profile data”). The profile data may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, profile pictures, gender, date of birth, relationship status, interests and hobbies, educational details and employment details. The profile data may be processed for the purposes of enabling and monitoring your use of our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is consent, namely the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.

2.5 We may process information contained in any enquiry you submit to us regarding products and/or services (“enquiry data”). The enquiry data may be processed for the purposes of offering, marketing and selling relevant products and/or services to you. The legal basis for this processing is the consent received from you.

2.6 We may process information relating to transactions, including purchases of goods and services, that you enter into with us and/or through our website (“transaction data”).  The transaction data may include your contact details and the transaction details.  The transaction data may be processed for the purpose of supplying the purchased goods and services and keeping proper records of those transactions. The legal basis for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract with a supplier and also our legitimate interests, namely our interest in the proper administration of our website and business.

2.7 We may process information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters (“notification data”). The notification data may be processed for the purposes of sending you the relevant notifications and/or newsletters. The legal basis for this processing is consent and the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.

2.8 We may process information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us (“correspondence data”). The correspondence data may include the communication content and metadata associated with the communication.  Our website will generate the metadata associated with communications made using the website contact forms.  The correspondence data may be processed for the purposes of communicating with you and record-keeping. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business and communications with users.

2.9 We may process any of your personal data identified in the other provisions of this policy where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the protection and assertion of our legal rights, your legal rights and the legal rights of others in accordance with the Limitations Act 1980.

2.10 In addition to the specific purposes for which we may process your personal data set out in this Section 3, we may also process any of your personal data where such processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject.

2.11 Please do not supply any other person’s personal data to us, unless we prompt you to do so.

3\. Providing your personal data to others

3.1 We may disclose your personal data to any member of our group of companies this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its subsidiaries insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.

3.2 We may disclose your personal data to our insurers and/or professional advisers insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes of obtaining and maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, obtaining professional advice and managing legal disputes.

3.3 We may disclose your passenger names, ages and booking itinerary to suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the fulfilment of the holiday contract.

3.4 Financial transactions relating to our website and services are handled by our payment services providers, Worldpay and Barclaycard Merchant Services. We will share transaction data with our payment services providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing your payments, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. You can find information about the payment services providers’ privacy policies and practices at [Worldpays](https://www.worldpay.com/uk/privacy-policy) & [Barclaycard Merchant Services](https://www.barclaycard.co.uk/personal/privacy-policy?ref=top-nav).

3.5 In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data set out in this Section 4, we may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

4\. International transfers of your personal data

4.1 In this Section 5, we provide information about the circumstances in which your personal data may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA)].

4.2 The hosting facilities for our website are situated in the United Kingdom and are thus within the EEA and subject to GDPR EU 2016/679.

4.3 Accommodation, Tours and transfer suppliers are situated in the USA, Africa, Australia, Egypt and Asia.  Countries outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) do not always offer the same levels of protection to your personal data, so European law has prohibited transfers of personal data outside of the EEA unless the transfer meets certain criteria.

Some of our third parties service providers are based outside the European Economic Area (EEA) so their processing of your personal data will involve a transfer of data outside the EEA.

Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we do our best to ensure a similar degree of security of data by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is in place:

We will only transfer your personal data to countries that the European Commission have approved as providing an adequate level of protection for personal data by; or  
Where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts or codes of conduct or certification mechanisms approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe; or  
If we use US-based providers that are part of EU-US Privacy Shield, we may transfer data to them, as they have equivalent safeguards in place.  
If none of the above safeguards is available, we may request your explicit consent to the specific transfer. You will have the right to withdraw this consent at any time.

5\. Retaining and deleting personal data

5.1 This Section 6 sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations in relation to the retention and deletion of personal data.

5.2 Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.

5.3 We will retain and delete your personal data as follows:

(a) All information taken at the time of booking will be retained for 36 months following your trip return date, at the end of which period it will be deleted from our in-house system, unless you have any future reservations made with us.  In these cases the information will be deleted 36 months after your final trip with us.

5.4 Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section 6, we may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

6\. Amendments

6.1 We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.

6.2 You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this policy.

7\. Your rights

7.1 You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you; provision of such information will be subject to:

(a) the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity for this purpose, we will usually accept an email from the lead passenger via the email address provided at the time of booking or a posted letter.

7.2 We may withhold personal information that you request to the extent permitted by law.

7.3 You may instruct us at any time not to process your personal information for marketing purposes.

7.4 In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes.

8\. Your rights

8.1 In this Section 8, we have summarised the rights that you have under data protection law. Some of the rights are complex, and not all of the details have been included in our summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant laws and guidance from the regulatory authorities for a full explanation of these rights.

8.2 Your principal rights under data protection law are:

(a) the right to access;

(b) the right to rectification;

(c) the right to erasure;

(d) the right to restrict processing;

(e) the right to object to processing;

(f) the right to data portability;

(g) the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and

(h) the right to withdraw consent.

8.3 You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not we process your personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information. That additional information includes details of the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data. Providing the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. We will not charge for subject access requests unless they are ‘excessive’ (e.g. repetitive). You should receive a response to your request within 30 days of our receiving it.

You can access your personal data by emailing legal@2bookaholiday.com.

8.4 You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.

8.5 In some circumstances you have the right to the erasure of your personal data without undue delay. Those circumstances include: the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed; you withdraw consent to consent-based processing; the processing is for direct marketing purposes; and the personal data have been unlawfully processed. However, there are certain general exclusions of the right to erasure. Those general exclusions include where processing is necessary: for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information; for compliance with a legal obligation; or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

8.6 In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection. Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data. However, we will only otherwise process it: with your consent; for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of important public interest.

8.7 You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of any official authority vested in us; or the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we will cease to process the personal information unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

8.8 You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, we will cease to process your personal data for this purpose.

8.9 To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal data is consent, and such processing is carried out by automated means, you have the right to receive your personal data from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. However, this right does not apply where it would adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.

8.10 If you consider that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with the ICO as supervisory authority responsible for data protection in the UK.

8.11 To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.

8.12 You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us

9\. About cookies

9.1 A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

9.2 Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.

9.3 Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

10\. Cookies that we use

10.1 We use cookies for the following purposes:

(a) authentication – we use cookies to identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website.

(b) status – we use cookies to help us to determine if you are logged into our website.

(c) personalisation – we use cookies to store information about your preferences and to personalise the website for you.

(d) security – we use cookies as an element of the security measures used to protect user accounts, including preventing fraudulent use of login credentials, and to protect our website and services generally.

(e) analysis – we use cookies to help us to analyse the use and performance of our website and services.

(f) cookie consent – we use cookies to store your preferences in relation to the use of cookies more generally.

11\. Cookies used by our service providers

11.1 Our service providers use cookies and those cookies may be stored on your computer when you visit our website.

11.2 We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website.  For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.

11.3 We publish Google AdSense advertisements on our website. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the web using cookies. This behaviour tracking allows Google to tailor the advertisements that you see on other websites to reflect your interests (but we do not publish interest-based advertisements on our website). You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting [Googles Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the AdSense partner network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s [multi-cookie opt-out mechanism. ](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you may wish to consider using the [Google browser plug-ins](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996).[ The relevant cookies are: [identify cookies].]

12\. Managing cookies

12.1 Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:

(a) [Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en);

(b) [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences);

(c) [Opera](http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/);

(d) [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies);

(e) [Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411);

(f) [Edge](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy).

12.2 Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.

12.3 If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our website.

13\. Our details

13.1 We are registered in England and Wales under registration number 5642720 and our registered office is at The Old Forge, Hoults Yard, Hoults Estate, Newcastle Upon Tyne, NE6 1AB.

13.2 Our principal place of business is at Westmead House, Farnborough, Hampshire, GU14 7LP

13.3 You can contact us:

(a) by post, using the postal address given above

(b) using our website contact form;

(c) by telephone, on the contact number published on our website.

(d) by email, using the email address published on our website.

14\. Data protection manager

14.1 Our data protection manager’s contact details are:  DPM@2bookaholiday.com

We pride ourselves on good customer service, take a look at our feefo reviews and see for yourself!

Our average score from **193** reviews.

> Great customer service, very helpful able to sort out a short break at a great hotel, and flights. I would recommend this company to my friends, and I will certainly be using them again. 

> It’s a great hotel. Services n customers care exemplary. The selection of food is gastronomic ,credit to the chefs . The cakes in the coffee cafe melts in your mouth n out of this world. Planning to go back end of this year with a group of friends to celebrate our birthdays 

Mrs Lynette Hepworth

> Everything sorted apart from choosing seats on the plane . Hassle free holiday. 

Mrs SHIRLEY HOWARD

> Would recommend and buy again 

All reviews are from [FeeFo](https://ww2.feefo.com/en-US/reviews/going-luxury?displayFeedbackType=BOTH&timeFrame=ALL). You can view all our [reviews here](https://ww2.feefo.com/en-US/reviews/going-luxury?displayFeedbackType=BOTH&timeFrame=ALL)

## Favourites

If you find a holiday you like just click on the __button to save it and view it later. All your saved/favourite holiday deals will appear here!.

© 2020 Going Luxury. All rights reserved. | Travel Website by [Clark Studios](http://www.clark-studios.co.uk/)
